charismaoncommand.com 2019-11-14

# Privacy Policy - Charisma on Command

#### BY VISITING THIS WEB SITE, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**OVERVIEW**

It is Charisma On Command, (“Charisma On Commands,” “we”, “our”, “the company” or “us”) policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect, how we use the information and how you can control what you provide us.

This Privacy Policy also incorporates our Security Policy, our Cookie Policy and our Third Party Infrastructure Policy.

For purposes of this policy, the term “personal data” is used to describe any type of data that obtained, collected, and used by Charisma On Command.

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

**Information You Provide Us**  
Charisma On Command may collect the following personally-identifying information:

  * contact information including name, email address, username and billing address
  * billing information including credit card details
  * interactions such as views and likes of videos
  * preferences or settings that determine a consistent experience on our service
  * comments made on private groups (Facebook group, future forums)
  * your internet protocol (IP) address
  * feedback or requests for support
  * user content, to the extent that you choose to input personally-identifying data as part of presentations, images, comments, and other content that you post to or through our service

The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our First Impressions module to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Charisma On Command – by purchasing a paid product, for example Charisma University – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions.

**Information We Collect Automatically**  
Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. As you navigate through our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies (including Google Analytics, sites that partner with Google and others) to collect certain information about your browsing actions, and patterns. This will generally include information about your location, your traffic pattern through our website, and any communications between your computer and our Website. Among other things, we will collect data about the type of computer you use, your Internet connection, your IP address, your browser type, search history and YouTube history.

The information we collect automatically is used for statistical data and will not include personal information. We use this data to improve our Website and our service offerings. To the extent that you voluntarily provide personal information to us, our systems will associate the automatically collected information with your personal information.

**Cookies And Pixels**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Charisma On Command uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. Our visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. The Company reserves the right to use technological equivalents of cookies, including social media pixels. These pixels allow social media sites to track visitors to outside websites so as to tailor advertising messages users see while visiting that social media website. The Company reserves the right to use these pixels in compliance with the policies of the various social media sites.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
Charisma On Command may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, we may monitor the most popular page on our website. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others. Visitors can choose choose to disable cookies using their web browsers, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Third Party Links**  
The Site may contain links to third party websites. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our Site. Other sites accessible through this Site via links or otherwise have their own policies in regard to privacy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties. Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

**Children And Our Services**  
To access or use the Site, you must be 16 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy. Children under the age of 16 are prohibited from using the Site. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. In addition, we comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Article 8 requirements. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**HOW INFORMATION IS USED**

Charisma On Command uses information it collects to deliver our service to you and continuously enhance your experience. If you are a subscriber to our email list, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about other products, solicit your feedback, or just send you content from our blog. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. In example: as in publish in social media, testimonials, etc. From time-to-time, we may use the information you provide to us to make you offers to purchase products and services provided by third parties in exchange for a commission to be paid to us by such third parties. Should you opt to take part in such promotions, the third parties will receive your information.

From time-to-time, we may use the information you provide to us to display advertisements to you that are tailored to your personal characteristics, interests, and activities.

**WITH WHOM INFORMATION IS SHARED**

Charisma On Command uses certain third-party services to enhance your user experience, collect public-information about visitors and collect and process payments securely.

Charisma On Command discloses personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our websites, and that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using our websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Additionally, Charisma On Command may disclose personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Charisma On Command believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of our, third parties or the public at large.

Charisma On Command will not rent or sell personally-identifying information to anyone.

**Business Transfers**  
If Charisma On Command or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Charisma On Command goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Charisma On Command may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**HOW YOU CAN CONTROL THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Charisma On Command collects personally-identifying information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Charisma On Command. We do not store credit card details that are entered at the time of purchase, that information is sent directly to Stripe and PayPal and we only store the necessary references to your account such that we can securely interact with our payment processor. You can control which information you supply at any time, with the caveat that it may prevent you from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**EU PERSONAL DATA**

If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, Switzerland, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) related to your personal data, as further described below. Charisma On Command will be the controller of your personal data processed in connection with the service.

**Email Information**  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail, and telephone. This also applies when you register for our website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site. For further information see the email policies below.

**Accessing, Correcting, And Deleting Your Personal Data**  
You have certain rights with respect to your personal data, and we want to help you review and update your information to ensure it is accurate and up-to-date. For more information or any additional requests you can contact us via [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

  * **Access:** You can request more information about the personal data we hold about you and request a copy of such personal data.
  * **Rectification:** If you believe that any personal data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data.
  * **Erasure:** You can request that we erase some or all of your personal data from our systems.
  * **Portability:** You can ask for a copy of your personal data in a machine-readable format.
  * **Restriction of processing:** You can request restriction of processing by contacting [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Visitors’ GDPR Rights**  
If you are within the European Union, you are entitled to certain information and have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation. Those rights include:

  * We will retain any information you choose to provide to us until the earlier of: (a) you asking us to delete the information, (b) our decision to cease using our existing data providers, or (c) the Company decides that the value in retaining the data is outweighed by the costs of retaining it.
  * You have the right to request access to your data that the Company stores and the rights to either rectify or erase your personal data.
  * You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your data.
  * You have the right to object to the processing of your data and the right to the portability of your data.
  * To the extent that you provided consent to the Company’s processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent.
  * You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection Regulation.

To exercise these rights please email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.

**HOW INFORMATION IS PROTECTED**

Charisma On Command takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. Your account is protected by a password you set and are responsible for keeping safe. When entering information into our system such as passwords or financial information, all if this is done securely using SSL. Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Credit Card information and other sensitive information is never transmitted via email.

Charisma on Command may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. We maintain security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure. However, no exchange of data over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you. While we make every effort to protect the personal information you share with Charisma On Command , you acknowledge that this information could be accessed or tampered with by a third party. You agree that we are not responsible for any intercepted information shared through Charisma On Command without knowledge or permission. Additionally, you release Charisma On Command from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

**International Privacy Laws**  
If you are a member from outside of the United States, please be aware that you are sending data, including personally identifying information, to the United States where our servers are located. That information may then be transferred within the United States and then transferred back out of the United States to countries outside of your residence, depending upon the type of information and how it is stored by us. Our collection, storage and use of your personal information will at all times continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy.

**Updating Your Information**  
You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by contacting us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Changes To This Policy**  
You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. We will revise and update the policy as necessary and if changes are made to this policy, a new privacy policy will be posted on our site, with a date of change.

**Dispute Resolution**  
We commit to working with you to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy should contact us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Contact**  
If you have questions about our privacy policy, please email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Updated: November 2018
